https://oslosweatershop.com/en/content/5-privacy

Shopping cart
Handlekurv 0 Produkt Produkter
(tom)
Gå til kasse
Home > PrivacyPrivacyThis Privacy Policy applies only to information that is provided to us through this Site.SecurityOslo Sweater Shop is very concerned with safeguarding your information. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).Collection and UseOur main reason for collecting information is to provide and improve our Site, services, features and content, and to enable users to easily navigate our site-Personal InformationWe use the personal information you provide mainly to provide the service, process your transactions and administer your inquiries.We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other users to improve the quality and value of the Service and to analyze and understand how our Site and Service are used.We may also use your email to contact you with marketing and promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you.When you visit our site our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website.  This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s browser type, pages of our site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our site, access times and dates, and other statistics. We use this information to monitor and analyze use of the site and the service and for the site’s technical administration, to increase our site’s functionality and user-friendliness.Cookies and Pixel TagsWe use cookies to collect information for two purposes. First, we use persistent cookies to save your login information for future logins to the site. Second, we use session ID cookies to enable certain features of the site, to better understand how you interact with the site.We may also use pixel tag, which is an electronic image, often a single pixel that is ordinarily not visible to users and may be associated with cookies on a user’s hard drive. Pixel tags allow us to count users who have visited certain pages of the site.Information SharingWe may share aggregated information that does not include Personal Information and we may otherwise disclose Non-Identifying Information and Log Data with third parties for industry analysis, demographic profiling, and to deliver targeted advertising about other products and services. Any aggregated information shared in these contexts will not contain your personal information.Changing or Deleting Your InformationAll customers may update, correct or delete the personal information in their registration profile by contacting us or by making edits in the My Account section of the site. If you would like us to delete your account in our system, please contact us.Links to Other SitesOur Site contains links to other websites that should follow the same rules regarding the use or disclosure of the personal information you submit.Contacting UsIf you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at sweater@online.no
